Guide to the Claire Kincannon theatre collection, 1955-2011
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Washington, D.C., 1971-2011; (24 boxes)
  - Headshots (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Photographs of Elizabeth Taylor, Mia Dillon, Zev Bufman, Peter Gallagher.
  - "Growth from Within", Arena Stage, circa 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - America's Arena, for Arena Stage Subscribers and Associates, 1984-1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Vol. 2, no. 2; Vol. 3, no. 1-2; Vol. 4, no. 1-2; Vol. 5, no. 2; Vol. 6, no. 1-3; Vol. 7, no. 1
  - Annual Reports, Arena Stage, 1983-1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Reports.
  - The Arena Stage Campaign, ca. May, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Gannett, ca. 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Articles.
  - Ozzy Osbourne, April, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Press Releases; Photograph.
  - Show Case on the Arts, Georgetown University, Spring, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Howard's End, Smithsonian Institution Resident Associate Program, ca. March, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Newspaper Articles; Photograph.
  - Cultural Alliance, ca. February, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Newsletter.
  - Desert Island Discs, WETA, September 8, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Various Photographs (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Concerts, National Gallery of Art, June 29, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Annual Reports; Schedules; Publication.
  - Invitations (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Invitations for plays not attended or no playbills.
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Photographs.
  - Miscellaneous Invitations (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Invitations.
  - Photographs from the Wayside Theatre, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Seven photographs.
  - Miscellaneous playbills, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Victor Borge and his Concert Orchestra
    Spies in your eyes, JCA Playguild
    Hamlet, Philharmonia Orchestra
    Henry V: An interpretation of the Photoplay
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Magazine and newspaper articles, Fall 1976-2007 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - New York Times, Washington Post, articles, March 21, 1990-May 8, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Invitations, press releases, circa 1980-2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, season previews, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    From Washington DC and Virginia theatres
  - Season previews, 1991-2006 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Includes schedules from: Arena Stage, Kennedy Center, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, Theatre J, Washington National Opera, Woolly Mammoth
  - Season previews, 2006-2007 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Includes schedules from: Arena Stage, Ford's Theatre, Kennedy Center, PEN/Faulkner Foundation, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, The Studio Theatre, Washington National Opera, Washington Performing Arts Society, Wayside Theatre, Woolly Mammoth
  - Season previews, 2007-2011 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Marilyn Monroe: Life as a Legend
    Franklin Park Performing and Visual Arts Center (2008-2009)
    Grease at the Olney Theatre Center
    Shenandoah Summer Music Theatre (2011)
  - Season previews, 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Includes schedules from: Arena Stage, George Mason University's Center for the Arts, Kennedy Center, Olney, PEN/Faulkner Foundation, Folger Theatre, Shenandoah Conservatory, The Studio Theatre, Theatre J, University of Notre Dame, Washington National Opera, Washington Performing Arts Society
  - Season previews, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Includes schedules from: Arena Stage, Contemporary American Theatre Festival, Olney, Folger Theatre, Shakespeare Theatre Company, Shenandoah Conservatory, Signature Theatre, Strathmore Music Center, The Studio Theatre, Theatre J, Washington National Cathedral, Washington National Opera, Woolly Mammoth
  - Season previews, 2009-2011 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Includes schedules from: Arena Stage, Kennedy Center, Master Singers of Virginia, Washington National Opera
  - Museum brochures, 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Librettos for Aida, La Sonnambula, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Choruses of the Pirates of Penzance, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Stratford and Shaw festivals, Canada, 2006-2009 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Programs; Playbills.
- Series 2: Ohio Regional Theatres, 1945-2007; (5 boxes)
  The second series covers Kincannon's early interest in theatre while in the Ohio area (1955-1982). It contains mostly playbooks and programs from area performances.
  - On the Town, Auditorium Theatre, Memphis, TN, circa 1945 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Playbill; Program.
  - The Voice of the Turtle, Selwyn Theatre, Chicago, IL, October 7, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Rebecca, Chief Theatre, Colorado Springs, CO, November 2, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Cincinatti Symphony Orchestra, Music Hall, Cincinatti, OH, November 10-11, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - The Ballet Theatre coast to coast tour, Auditorium, Memphis, TN, 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, Auditorium, Memphis, TN, January 9, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Paul Draper and Larry Adler, Auditorium, Memphis, TN, February 26, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Philharmonics playbills, 1946-1961 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Dayton Philharmonic Orchestra, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH
    Philharmonic-Symphony Society of New York, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH
  - The Glass Menagerie, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, January 8, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Oklahoma, Cox Theatre, Cincinatti, OH, February 17-23, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Apple of His Eye, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, February 19, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Lauritz Melchior, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, March 26, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Lily Pons, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, April 10, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Call Me Mister, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, April 21, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Paul Whiteman and His Company, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, April 28, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Assorted Ohio playbills, 1947-1960 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    The Antioch yellow springs festival, OH
    Light up the sky, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH
    The magnificent Yankee, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH
    O mistress mine, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH
    Pick-up girl, Ellis Auditorium, Memphis, TN
    State of the union, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH
    The wise have not spoken, Yellow Springs Area Theatre, OH
  - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, January 3, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Man and Superman, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, circa January 24, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Private Lives, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, circa January-February 1948 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Song of Norway, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, March 15, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Carousel, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, November 15-17, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis; Rudy Vallee, Beverly Hills Country Club, Newport, KY, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    Playbills.
  - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, January 8, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Harvey, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, January 24-26, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, March 7, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo, RKO Keith Theatre, OH, January 16, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Saint Joan, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, 1954-1955 Season (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Playbook; Program.
  - The Dark is Light Enough, Cox Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, 1954-1955 Season (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The King and I, Kieth's Theatre, Dayton, OH, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The Seven Year Itch, The Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, January, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - American Play Parade, Wilmington College Summer Theatre, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Announcement.
  - Broadway Highlights, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Teahouse of the August Moon, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Macbeth and Twelfth Night, Antioch Area Theatre, Antioch College, OH, 1955 season (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Program; Playbook.
  - Come Back, Little Sheba, Cincinnati Summer Playhouse, OH, 1955 Season (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Reclining Figure, Euclid-77th St. Theatre, Cleveland Playhouse, 1955-1956 Season (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Bus Stop, The Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Damn Yankees, The Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Boyfriend, The Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, April, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - The Boyfriend, Hartman Theatre, Columbus, OH, April, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - The Rainmaker, Trotwood-Madison Circle Theatre, OH, June, July, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Arms and the Man, Trotwood-Madison Circle Theatre, OH, July, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - King Lear, Antioch Area Theatre, Antioch College, OH, 1956 Season (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - The Young and the Beautiful, Cincinnati Summer Playhouse, OH, July, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Blithe Spirit, Cincinnati Summer Playhouse, OH, July, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - An Evening With Tennessee Williams, Cincinnati Summer Playhouse, OH, August, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Renovation of the Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, September, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Souvenir Program.
  - A Hatful of Rain, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, December, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The Cleveland Orchestra, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, March 13, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, Colonial Theatre, Dayton, OH, March, ca. 1957-58 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - South Pacific, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, June, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter?, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, June, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - The Soldier's Tale, Trouble in Tahiti, and Lost in the Stars, Antioch Area Theatre, Antioch College, OH, 1957 Season (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Primrose Path, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, July, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, July, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Petticoat Fever, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, July, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Brigadoon, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, July, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - The Moon is Blue, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, July, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Can-Can, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, August, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Guys and Dolls, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, August, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Show Boat, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, September, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - No Time For Sergeants, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, September, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - The Egghead, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, September, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Lecture: Mme. Vijaya Lakshmi Pandit, Dayton Council on World Affairs, NCR Auditorium, OH, November 4, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - La Traviata, NBC Opera Company, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, November 26, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - The Waltz of the Toreadors, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Dark of the Moon, Wilmington College Summer Theatre, OH, ca. 1957 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Auntie Mame, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, March, April, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Auntie Mame, Memorial Theatre, Dayton, OH, ca. 1958 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - The Music Man, Dayton, OH, circa 1959 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Once Upon a Mattress, Dayton, OH, circa 1959 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - The King and I, Cincinnati Star Theatre, September, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - The Student Prince, Cincinnati Star Theatre, September, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Guys and Dolls, Cincinnati Star Theatre, September, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Carousel, Cincinnati Star Theatre, September, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - A Mighty Man is He, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, November, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Sweet Bird of Youth, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, May 2, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - The World of Suzie Wong, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, May 23, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - The 1960 Cincinnati Summer Opera at the Zoo!, Zoo Opera Pavilion, Cincinnati, OH, June 23-July 23, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - A Taste of Honey, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, September, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - The Pleasure of His Company, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, December 16-17, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Fiorello!, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, ca. 1960 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - The World of Suzie Wong, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, ca. 1960 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - The Andersonville Trial, Memorial Hall, Dayton, OH, February 3-4, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - I Do, I Do, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, November, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    Program; Curtain Call.
  - Hello, Dolly!, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of June 15, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Pleasure of His Company, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of June 22, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - The Most Happy Fella, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of July, 13, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Send Me No Flowers, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of July 20, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Forty Carats, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of August 3, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Great Waltz, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of August 10, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Anything Goes, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of August 17, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Catch Me If You Can, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 24, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Sound of Music, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 31, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Butterflies are Free, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1971-1972 season (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Company, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1971-1972 season (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Promises, Promises, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1971-1972 season (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - The Last of the Red Hot Lovers, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1971-1972 season (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - The Me Nobody Knows, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1971-1972 season (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Will Roger's U.S.A., American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1971-1972 season (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - And Miss Reardon Drinks a Little, Shubert Theatre Cincinnati, OH, November, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - The Gingerbread Lady, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, January, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Can-Can, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 13, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Moon is Blue, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 20, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - 1776, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 27, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Oklahoma, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 11, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 18, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Meet Me in St. Louis, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 25, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Come Blow Your Horn, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    Playbook.
  - Milk and Honey, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of August 1, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Good News, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 15, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Everybody Loves Opal, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 22, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Music in the Air, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 29, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Applause, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1972-1973 Season (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Sleuth, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1972-1973 season (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Promises, Promises, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 12, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Born Yesterday, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of June 19, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Guys and Dolls, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 26, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - My Daughter's Rated X, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 3, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - The Music Man, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 10, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - The Pajama Game, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 17, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - How the Other Half Loves, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 24, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - South Pacific, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 31, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 7, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Applause, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 14, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - The Prisoner of Second Avenue, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 21, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Once Upon a Mattress, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 28, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, August, September, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Butley, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, November, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Grease, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1973-1974 season (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - No, No, Nanette, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1973-1974 season (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Twigs, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1973-1974 season (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1973-1974 season (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - The Waltz of the Toreadors, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, February. 1974 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Good News, Shubert Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - R.S.V.P. The Cole Porters, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, ca. 1974 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - No, No, Nanette, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 11, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Finishing Touches, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of June 18, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kiss Me Kate, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 25, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Mother is Engaged, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 3, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 9, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sunday in New York, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 16, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Take Me Along, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 23, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Tunnel of Love, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 30, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Gigi, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 6, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 6 Rms Riv Vu, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 13, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Oliver, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 20, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Luv, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of 27, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Pippin, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1974-1975 season (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Seesaw, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, 1974-1975 season (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Move Over Mrs. Markham, American Theatre League of Dayton, OH, ca. 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Dayton Philharmonic Orchestra, Seasons 1974-75, 1975-76, 1976-77 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Sugar, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 10, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Bus Stop, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 17, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - On a Clear Day, You Can See Forever, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 24, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Stop, Thief, Stop!!, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 1, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - She Loves Me, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 8, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Under the Yum Yum Tree, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 15, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Peter Pan, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 22, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - The Cooch Dancer, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 29, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Bitter Sweet, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 5, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Private Lives, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 12, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Mock and Mabel, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 19, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - The Boy Friend, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 26, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Room Service, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 15, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Irene, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 29, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Norman, Is That You?, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, Week of June 29, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 6, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Damn Yankees, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 13, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Panama Hattie, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 20, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Shenandoah, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 27, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Accent on Youth, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 3, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Funny Girl, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 10, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - The Student Prince, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 17, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - George Washington Slept Here, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 24, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - A Little Night Music, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 31, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - An Evening with Dom De Luise, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of September 7, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Kismet, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of June 28, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Wonderful Town, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of July 26, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Li'l Abner, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 2, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Grease, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 16, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Make a Million, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, week of August 23, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Hello, Dolly!, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - I Love My Wife, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Side By Side By Sondheim, Victory Theatre Association, Dayton, OH, September, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - My Fair Lady, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Grease, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Brigadoon, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Side by Side by Sondheim, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 4 Girls 4, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bob Fosse's Dancin', Taft Theatre, Cincinnati, OH, November, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Bob Fosse's Dancin', Dayton, OH, ca. 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Ain't Misbehavin', ca. 1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Joffrey II: The Joffrey Ballet, Victory Theatre, January, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - The Fantasticks, Victory Theatre Season, Virginia's Barter Theatre, Dayton, OH, March, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - The Madwoman of Central Park West, Victory Theatre, Dayton, OH, April, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - George M, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Greenwich Scandals of 1923, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - The New 4 Girls, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, July 27-August 1, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - The Pirates of Penzance, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, August 10-15, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - The Unsinkable Molly Brown, Kenley Players, Dayton, OH, August 17-22, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Various Concerts, Civic Music Association (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, Schuster Center, Dayton, OH, April 17-22, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Series 3: Broadway and London Productions, 1955-2007; (3 boxes)
  The third series is the collection of Broadway and London productions Kincannon attended from 1955-2007. This series consists of mostly playbills and programs.
  - Ice-Capades, NYC, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Born Yesterday, Lyceum Theatre, NYC, August 16, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Sadler's Wells Ballet, NYC, 1950-1951 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Cherry Orchard, 4th Street Theatre, NYC, ca. October 18, 1955 - January 15, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ANTA Album, Adelphi Theatre, NYC, March 28, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Concerts and Poetry Readings, NYC, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Calendar.